Hill, James C. Arbitration Files 5538
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II - Arbitration Files
  - Sub-Series A. Board of Education (New York City and Others)
    - United Federation of Teachers, Local 2, American Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      10/22/1973; #1339- 0072-73 Issues: Compensation (Per Diem vs. Regular Substitutes); Termination of Employment.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      2/14/1975; #1339-0398-73 Settled.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      10/16/1974; #1330-0844-73 Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      12/3/1973; #1339-1300-73 No Decision, Issues: Hours; Rates of Pay.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      9/16/1974; #1339-1389-73 No Decision, Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
    - North Bellmore Union Free School District #4 Board of Education vs. North Bellmore Teachers Association, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      9/10/73; #1339-0359-72 Issues: Leaves of Absence; Assignment of Jobs.
    - Philadelphia School District vs. Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, Local 3., 1973 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      11/19/1973; #1439-0015-72M Issue: Seniority.
    - Philadelphia Board of Education vs. Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, Local 3, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      10/20/1971; #1439-0536-71J Withdrawn.
    - Seaford Union Free School District #6 Board of Education vs. Seaford Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      6/18/74; #1339-1404-73 Issues: Sick Leave; Sick Pay.
    - Wantagh Board of Education vs. Wantagh Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      10/7/1974; #1339-0275-74 Settled.
    - Waterbury Board of Education vs. Waterbury Teachers Association, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      5/8/1971; #1239-0184-70 Issue: Promotion.
    - Windsor Board of Education vs. Windsor School Employees Union, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      11/4/1972; #1239-0001-72 Issues: Contract Interpretation; Promotion; Definition of "Concomitant".
    - City of Yonkers Board of Education vs. Yonkers Federation of Teachers, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 8)
      7/24/1972; #1339-0318-72 Fact-finding. Issues: Discharge; Improper Personal Conduct.
  - Sub-Series B. Arbitration Files
    Includes Awards of Arbitrators, Correspondence, Notes, Financial Material (Arbitrators' Bills), Agreements, Company Exhibits and Union Exhibits
    - Ace Novelty Company vs. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Local 169., 1957 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      10/10/57; Issues: Rates of Pay; Assignment of Jobs.
    - Acme Hamilton Corporation vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 206., 1963 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      6/24/1963; Postponed.
    - Acme Markets, Inc. vs. Meat Cutters, Butcher Workmen and Affiliated Crafts of North America, Local 1, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      12/10/1969; Issues: Demotion; Incompetence.
    - Acme Markets, Inc. vs. Retail Clerks International Association, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      9/21/72, 10/20/72; Postponed.
    - Airco Speer Electrodes and Anodes vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      9/29/1969; Issues: Discharge; Absences.
    - Alan Wood Steel Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      3/24/1959; Issues: Discharge; Insubordination.
    - Alan Wood Steel Company, Scrub Oaks Mine Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4303, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      6/1/1960; Issues: Plant Closure; Layoff; Seniority; Hours of Work; Premium Pay; Vacation.
    - Albemanle Paper Company vs. United Paperworkers International Union, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      4/3/1974; Withdrawn.
    - Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 1509, District 157, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      2/25/1967; Issues: Assignment of Jobs Outside of Classification; Overtime.
    - Allegheny Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2478, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 10)
      2/28/1975; Issues: Classification of Jobs; Incentives.
    - Allegheny Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2478, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      6/3/1974; Issues: Job Assignments; Seniority.
    - Allegheny Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2478, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 12)
      4/22/1974; Issues: Reduction in Force; Seniority.
    - Allegheny Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2478., 1973 (Box 64, Folder 13)
      1/4/1973; Issue: Vacations.
    - Allied Building Metal Industries vs. International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Local 455, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 14)
      12/3/1962; Issues: Vacations; Vacation Pay.
    - Allied Maintenance Corporation vs. Building Service Employees International Union, Local 176, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 15)
      7/16/1958; Issues: Discharge; Plant Rules.
    - American Airlines vs. L.D. Bearce, Transport Workers Union of America., 1961 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      1/13/1961; M-9-61 Issues: Suspension; Insubordination.
    - American Airlines vs. H.R. Courtney, Transport Workers Union of America, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      11/17/1961; M-195-61 Issues: Discharge; Absences.
    - American Airlines vs. J.W. Brotherton, Transport Workers Union of America -, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      11/22/1961; M-289-60 Issues: Suspension; Negligence and Carelessness.
    - American Airlines vs. F. Morgan, Transport Workers Union of America, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      11/22/1961; M-107-61 Issues: Suspension; Incompetence; Inefficiency.
    - American Airlines vs. D. Yerger, Transport Workers Union of America, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      11/22/1961; M-81-61 Issues: Suspension; Negligence and Carelessness.
    - American Airlines vs. W.F. Schearer, Transport Workers Union of America, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      11/27/1961; M-79-61 Issues: Suspension; Insubordination.
    - American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Local 501, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      11/30/1961; M-102-61 Withdrawn.
    - American Airlines vs. N. Vandre, Transport Workers Union of America, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      12/15/1961; M-283-61 Issues: Discharge; Absences.
    - American Airlines vs. R.H. Altizer, Transport Workers Union of America, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      12/21/1961; M-280-61 Issues: Discharge; Improper Personal Conduct.
    - American Airlines vs. L. Rybak, Transport Workers Union of America, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      12/27/1961; M-185-60 Issues: Suspension; Improper Personal Conduct.
    - American Airlines vs. S.V. Young, Transport Workers Union of America, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      12/27/1961; M-177-61 Issue: Overtime.
    - American Airlines vs. J.J. Scorey, Transport Workers Union of America, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 12)
      12/28/1961; M-76-61 Issue: Fringe Benefits.
    - American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union of America, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 13)
      1/10/1962; M-93-61 and M-100-61 Issues: Fringe Benefits; Strikes; Slowdowns; Work Stoppage.
    - American Airlines vs. N. Long, Transport Workers Union of America, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 14)
      1/12/1962; M-106-61 Issue: Overtime.
    - American Airlines vs. W. Richmond, Transport Workers Union of America, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 15)
      1/20/1962; M-159-61 and M-160-61 Issue: Overtime.
    - American Airlines vs. J. Guthrie, Flight Engineers International Association, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 16)
      10/15/1962; F-1-62 Issues: Employee Rights; Compensation.
    - American Airlines vs. Scope., 1961 (Box 65, Folder 17)
      M-132-61 Empty.
    - American Airlines vs. W.S. Frawley, Transport Workers Union of America, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 18)
      2/8/1962; M-196-61 Issues: Layoffs; Assignment to Work Outside Classification; Contracting Out.
    - American Airlines vs. C.A. Sweet, Transport Workers Union of America, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 19)
      7/18/1967; M-151-66 Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
    - American Airlines vs. C.F. Hill, Transport Workers Union of America, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 20)
      7/19/1967; M-332-66 Issue: Overtime.
    - American Airlines vs. W.L. Milligan, et. al., Transport Workers Union of America, Local 514, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 21)
      7/19/1967; S-38-65 Issue: Removal of Work from Bargaining Unit.
    - American Airlines vs. C. Cherry and H. Leathers, Transport Workers Union of America, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 22)
      11/14/1967; M-201-65 Issue: Contracting Out.
    - American Airlines vs. R.A. Kramer, et. al., Transport Workers Union of America; American Airlines vs. S.E. Johnson, Transport Workers Union of America, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 23)
      11/14/1967; M-14-65 Issues: Assignment of Jobs; Classification of Jobs.
    - American Airlines vs. D McCue, Transport Workers Union of America; American Airlines vs. R. Mullady, Transport Workers Union of America, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 24)
      11/15/1967; S-27-64 Issues: Contracting Out; Timeliness.
    - American Airlines vs. C. Guidance, Transport Workers Union of America, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      2/14/1968; M-288-66 Issues: Seniority; Layoffs; Transfers.
    - American Airlines vs. J. Lynch, Transport Workers Union of America, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      2/14/1968; M-92-66 Issue: Termination of Employment.
    - American Airlines vs. K.C. Hayes, Transport Workers Union of America, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      2/14/1968; M-137-65 Issue: Removal of Work From the Bargaining Unit.
    - American Airlines vs. T. Birmingham, Transport Workers Union of America, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      3/13/1968; M-138-65 Issues: Contracting Out; Assignment to Work Outside of Classification.
    - American Airlines vs. J. Lopes, Transport Workers Union of America, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      7/17/1968; M-101-68
    - American Airlines vs. O.W. Taylor, Transport Workers Union of America, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      9/26/1968; M-169-67 Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
    - American Airlines vs. R.J. Apker, Transport Workers Union of America, Local 514, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      9/26/1968; M-151-67 Issues: Assignment of Jobs; Seniority.
    - American Airlines vs. K.C. Hayes, Transport Workers Union of America, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      10/21/1968; M-85-67 Issue: Contracting Out.
    - American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union of America, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      1/22/1969; S-17-67 Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
    - American Airlines vs. W. Poppe, Transport Workers Union of America, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      1/22/1969; S-30-66 Issue: Contracting Out.
    - American Airlines vs. W.L. Milligan, et. al., Transport Workers Union of America, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      2/13/1970; S-19-65, S-22-65, S-23-65, S-24-65, S-25-65, S- 31-65 Issue: Contracting Out.
    - American Airlines vs. C.H. Hinesley, Transport Workers Union of America, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      9/10/1970; M-31-68 Issues: Assignment to Work Outside Classification; Overtime.
    - American Airlines - Work Assignments (Miscellaneous), 1953-1965 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - American Airlines - Subcontracting Cases (Miscellaneous) (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - American Airlines - Awards (Miscellaneous), 1968 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - American Airlines - System Board of Adjustment (Miscellaneous), 1961-1962 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - American Airlines - System Board of Adjustment (Miscellaneous), 1966-1968 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - American Airline Products, Inc. vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8673., 1970 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      10/27/1970; Issues: Absences; Call In.
    - American Broadcasting Company vs. National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      3/26/1965; Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
    - American Broadcasting Company vs. National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      7/11/1968; Postponed.
    - American Broadcasting Company vs. National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      5/29/1969; Postponed.
    - American Can Company vs. Federal Labor Union, Local 23393, 1958 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      8/4/58; #57-JCH-116 Issue: Classification of Jobs.
    - American Car and Laundry Division, ACF Industries, Inc. vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1625, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      1/5/72, 3/16/72/, 3/28/72; #H70-260; H69-1; H69-162, 163, 164, 165, 179, 180, 181, 182. Issues: Discharge, Alcoholism, Drinking, Intoxication; Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit; Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit, Supervisors and Foremen.
    - American Cyanamid Company vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 111, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      10/11/1961; L-30796 NY-L-301-61 Issues: Discharge; Absenteeism.
    - American Cyanamid Company vs. United Mine Workers of America, Local 12426, District 50, 1959 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      2/20/1959; Resolved and Withdrawn.
    - American Cyanamid Company vs. United Mine Workers of America, Local 12426, District 50, 1959 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      11/24/1959; Issues: Interpretation of Past Arbitration Award; Classification of Jobs.
    - American Cyanamid Company vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 143 -, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      7/14/1960; Issues: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit; Supervisors and Foremen.
    - American Cyanamid Company vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 111., 1961 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      10/11/1961; #L-30796 NY-L-301-61 Issue: Overtime.
    - American Cyanamid Company vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 111, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 12)
      12/19/1962; #L-30053 NY-L-495-62 Issues: Discharge; Financial Irresponsibility.
    - American Cyanamid Company vs. United Mine Workers of America, Local 12426, District 50, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 13)
      12/29/1962; Issue: Premium Pay.
    - American Cyanamid Company vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 111, 1964 (Box 68, Folder 14)
      8/25/1964; #L-39704 NY-L-670-63 Issue: Recall.
    - American Cyanamid Company vs. United Mine Workers of America, Local 12426, District 50 -, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 15)
      4/12/65; Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
    - American LaFrance, Division of Sterling Precision Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 421 -, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 16)
      12/30/1966; Issues: Seniority and Promotions; Suspension; Standards of Production; Contracting Out; Schedules of Work.
    - American Machine and Laundry Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 116, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 17)
      10/26/1961; #L-31669 NY-L-544-61 Issues: Discharge; Absences.
    - American Machine and Laundry Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 116, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 18)
      12/2/1961; #L-31106 NY-L-381-61 Issue: Classification of Jobs.
    - American Machine and Laundry Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 116, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 19)
      7/2/1965; #L-44670 NY-L-9331-64 Issue: Overtime.
    - American Machine and Laundry Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 365 -, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 20)
      7/8/68; #1330-0212-68 Issues: Suspension; Improper Job Attitude.
    - American Radiation and Sanitary Corporation, Detroit Controls Division vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 377, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 21)
      12/8/1960; #L-28782 HART-L-179-60 Issues: Discharge, Improper Personal Conduct.
    - American Radiation and Standard Sanitary Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 22)
      7/7/1961; #L-30272 NY-L-156-60 Issues: Suspension; Strikes; Slowdowns; Work Stoppages.
    - American Radiation and Sanitary Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1629, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 23)
      6/10/1961; #61A/1544 Issue: Removal of Work from Bargaining Unit.
    - American Sightseeing Tours, Inc. vs. Sightseeing Guides and Lecturers Union, Local 20076 of Greater New York, 1958 (Box 68, Folder 24)
      9/3/1958; #6249 Issues: Arbitration Procedure; Discharge; Incompetence; Inefficiency.
    - American Smelting and Refining Company vs. International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Local 365, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 25)
      12/15/1961; #61-44 Issue: Contracting Out.
    - American Smelting and Refining Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 143, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 26)
      9/20/1971; #70A/3776 Issues: Workweek; Premium Pay.
    - American Smelting and Refining Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 625, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 27)
      9/23/1970; #70A/7855 Withdrawn.
    - American Smelting and Refining Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 625, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 28)
      6/17/71; #70A/9306 Issue: Overtime.
    - American Smelting and Refining Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 365, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 29)
      8/29/1974; #18-0273 (TH-3) Issues: Posting; Supervisors and Foremen.
    - American Standard Industrial Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 897, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      6/26/65; #65A/2785 Issues: Discharge; Absence; Tardiness.
    - American Standard, Inc. vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1199, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      12/11/1970; #70A/7599 Resolved.
    - American Type Founders, Inc. vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 315, District 47, 1950 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      5/3/1950; Issue: Layoffs.
    - Amperex Electronic Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District Lodge 15 -, 1955 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      4/1/1955; Issue: Demotion.
    - Amperex Electronic Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District Lodge 15, 1960 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      7/27/1960; Issues: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit; Supervisors and Foremen.
    - Anaconda American Brass Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6445, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      5/31/65; #L-45664 HART-L-48-65 Opinion Missing.
    - Anaconda American Brass Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6445, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      8/22/1966; #AR-483 Issues: Demotion; Safety.
    - Anaconda American Brass Company vs. International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Local 593, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      3/24/1966; Issues: Discharge; Falsification.
    - Anaconda American Brass Company vs. United Mine Workers of America, Local 593, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      4/15/1969; Issue: Holiday Pay.
    - Anaconda American Brass Company vs. United Steelworkers of America -, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 10)
      2/22/1971; AR-1463 Withdrawn.
    - Anaconda Company, Raritan Copper Works vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4985 -, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 11)
      2/3/1975; #U-16-73 Issues: Past Practice; Schedules of Work.
    - Anchor Motor Freight, NY Corp. vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 469, 1956 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      1/31/1956; #55-107 Issues: Discharge; Negligence and Carelessness.
    - Anchor Motor Freight, Inc. vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 560, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 13)
      4/3/1967; #67/A2511 Withdrawn.
    - Anheuser Busch, Inc., New Jersey Brewers' Association vs. International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 68, 1959 (Box 69, Folder 14)
      2/12/1959; L-23127 NY-L- 673-58 Issue: Workweek.
    - Anheuser Busch, Inc. vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 102 -, 1961 (Box 69, Folder 15)
      2/9/1961; #L-26799 NY-L-121-60 Issues: Elimination of Jobs; Assignment of New Jobs.
    - Appalachian Steel Corporation vs. Steel, Metal, Alloys and Hardware Workers, Local 810, 1955 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      1/29/1955; #55-72 No Decision.
    - Arista Truck Renting Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District 157, 2006 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      4/3/2006; #67A/2269 Settled.
    - Arma Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 418, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      2/10/1962; Issue: Workweek.
    - Arma Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 418, 1963 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      2/10/1963; Issues: Classification of Jobs; Demotion.
    - Arma Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 418, 1963 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      2/10/1963; L-37870 NY-L-203-63 Withdrawn.
    - Arma Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 418, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      10/9/1964; #L-40360 NY-L-862-63 Issues: Recall; Supervisors and Foremen; Vacancies.
    - Arma Division of AMBAC Industries, Inc. vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 460, 1974 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      7/24/1974; #732 Issues: Duty to Bargain; Fringe Benefits; Insurance.
    - Armitage, John L. vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-406 -, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      1/5/68; #68A-1807 Issues: Discharge; Improper Job Attitude; Falsification.
    - Armstrong Cork Company vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 928, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 9)
      5/6/1970; #69A/6901 Issue: Assignment to Work Outside of Classification.
    - Armstrong Cork Company vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 285, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      9/9/1971; Issue: Reporting Pay.
    - Armstrong Cork Company vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 285, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 11)
      10/30/1975; Issue: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Art Chrome Company of America vs. United Furniture Workers of America, Local 136-B, 1948 (Box 70, Folder 12)
      6/22/1948; Issues: Discharge; Tardiness.
    - Atlas Chain and Precision Products Co., Inc. vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 271, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 13)
      9/22/1967; #14-30-0394-67 Withdrawn.
    - Avco Corporation vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 376 and 1010, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 14)
      6/22/67; Board of Inquiry Report to President of US Concerns Contract Negotiations.
    - Avco Corporation vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 376, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 15)
      9/28/1970; #12-30-0039-70 Withdrawn.
    - Babcock Printing Press Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 144, 1948 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      5/20/1948; #41A/112 Issues: Layoffs; Reduction of Hours; Shift Scheduling; Vacation Pay; Holiday Pay.
    - Baltimore Transit Authority vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 1300, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      9/30/1970; Issue: Contract Modification.
    - Bamberger, L. and Company vs. Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paper Hangers of America, District Council 10, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      10/26/1957; Issues: Discharge; Employees' Rights; Inability to Work.
    - Barker Engineering Corporation vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 726, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      11/26/1973; #1830-0151-73S Settled.